Contact

josedavids123@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jose-davidsauma-zaretsky-171b3823b (LinkedIn)

Contact - +573242780208 Top Skills

Java Development Spring Data MySQL

Certifications

JAVA Full-Stack Developer -Globant

JAVA Dev with Politenico de Colombia

Languages

English - Advanced Spanish - Native

Other Experiences

Military Service - One Year(2021 - 2022)

Honor mention serving with BACAIM6 - Marines Military Base

Jose David Sauma Zaretsky

Junior Java Software Developer | Java - SpringMVC-REST - Spring Security - PHP- MySQL - JDBC/JPA - JUnit - Git | Recruiter Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Summary

As a bilingual recruiter with 2 years of specialized experience in high-volume and financial recruitment within the BPO sector, I have developed a profound understanding of talent dynamics in the business environment. In addition to my human resources background, I am a passionate Java developer with expertise in technologies such as SpringMVC, REST, Spring Security, PHP, MySQL, JDBC/JPA, JUnit, and Git. My ability to merge the strategic vision of recruitment with technical skills in software development allows me to thoroughly grasp the needs of my team and ensure a perfect alignment between talent and projects. I am committed to continuous professional growth and the creation of highly efficient and collaborative teams. Let's connect and explore new opportunities together!

Experience

Freelance (Self employed)
Freelance Software Developer
October 2023 - Present (1 year)

Medellín Metropolitan Area

Various projects as a Freelancer developer

iQor

RecruiterNovember 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months) Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Solvo Global RecruiterMay 2022 - November 2022 (7 months)

Armada Nacional de Colombia Military ServiceApril 2021 - April 2022 (1 year 1 month) Coveñas, Sucre, Colombia

Solvo Global Collections SpecialistSeptember 2020 -April 2021 (8 months) Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Teleperformance
Customer Service AgentMarch 2019 January 2020 (11 months) Bogota, D.C.,
Capital District, Colombia

Education

Globant University

Computer Software and Media Applications · (February 2023 - February 2024)

Politécnico de Colombia
Technician, Computer Software Technology/Technician · (July 2022 - December 2023)

Politécnico de Colombia

Diploma of Education, Computer Software and Media Applications · (November 2022 - March 2023)

Colegio Retos

High School Diploma · (January 2017 - December 2018)